Caraline Dufrene

🗣 San Marcos, Texas, United States 🖼 caralinedufrene@gmail.com 🔲 2146203053 🛅 in/caraline-d

SUMMARY

Digital media student with two years of experience in scheduling, answering phones, timeliness, and engaging with customers. Proficient in Microsoft Outlook, Excel, and Word. Experienced in working in a fast-paced environment with tight deadlines. Strong aptitude for learning, with the ability to follow instructions.

EXPERIENCE

Intern

BanddDesign

August 2022 -November 2022, Austin, TX

- · Partnered alongside designers to create and install a project for a client.
- · Consistently organized office to better production.
- · Worked with the design team to order and receive materials for over 30 projects.

Facility Operator

Texas State Student Recreation Center

December 2021 - May 2022, San Marcos, TX

- •Monitored and maintained the facility during and before hours of operation.
- ·Led multiple opening shifts through opening doors, turning on facility lights, prepping for the day, and more.
- ·Completed sales and equipment rentals while multitasking.

Guest Service Representitive

Nothing Bundt Cakes

- August 2020 May 2021, Murphy, TX ·Opened and closed over thirty shifts.
- ·Helped train and lead four new hires.
- •Answered phones and responded to emails in a quick, professional manner.
- ·Generate additional revenue through upselling or add-on package selling.
- •Diffuse intense customer situations to maintain a high level of satisfaction.

PROJECTS

Summer Camp Counselor/ Photographer

Lonesome Dove Ranch · June 2020 - July 2022

- · Volunteered to take photos of fifty kids for multiple camps.
- · Patiently led three kids for a summer camp session
- · Worked on a team and developed strong communication skills.

Treasurer

Hope321 • May 2018 - Present

- ·Helped establish bylaws and goals for Hope321
- ·In charge of keeping track of useable funds and donations as well as sending out donation statements

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Digital Media Innovation

Minor in Business Administration ⋅ Texas State University ⋅ San Marcos, TX ⋅ 2023 ⋅ 4.0

High School Diploma

Wylie High School · Wylie, TX · 2021 · 4.0

SKILLS

Entry level HTML

Organized

Schedule management

Money Handling

Timliness

Experience answering phones

Customer Service